A Guide to the James J. Kilpatrick Papers 1959-1985
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Videocassette & Tape Recordings
  - Tape Recordings of "Agronsky and Company"
    - 89. Andropov Proposes a Ban on Anti-Staellite Weapons/Nazi War Criminal in U.S./Sen. Glenn Wants Reagan's Job 20 Aug 1983 (Box 50)
    - 90. Gender Gap Widens/Reagan's Women's Program a Sham/Military Action by French Troops in Chad vs. Libya/Assassination of Aquino & Effects Upon Marcos 27 Aug 1983 (Box 50)
    - 91. Soviets Shoot Down Korean Airliner/U.S. Marines in Beirut/Leadership Change in Israel 3 Sep 1983 (Box 50)
    - 92. Soviets and the Korean Airliner/Civil War in Lebanon/Women & Reagan/Conversation between Reagan & Kilpatrick 10 Sep 1983 (Box 50)
    - 93. War Powers Act & Lebanon/Defense Spending Bill/Carnegie Foundation & High School Education 17 Sep 1983 (Box 50)
    - 94. War Powers Resolution & Lebanon/Reagan Visit with Marcos/the U.S. & the U.N./What's with Watt? 24 Sep 1983 (Box 50)
    - 95. Congress, the War Powers Act, & Lebanon/the U.N./Trouble for the Airlines 1 Oct 1983 (Box 50)
    - 96. Presidential Campaign/U.S. Soviet Agreement on Arms Control/Martin Luther King, Jr./Watt 8 Oct 1983 (Box 50)
    - 97. President's Cabinet/Jordanian Strike Force/Lebanon/Presidential Campaign/15th Year of "Agronsky & Company" 15 Oct 19832 (Box 51)
    - 98. Reagan Comment re Martin Luther King, Jr./U.S. Aid to Nicaragua/Censorship of Government Employees/Organ Transplants 22 Oct 1983 (Box 51)
    - 99. Bombing in Beirut/Grenada Invasion 29 Oct 1983 (Box 51)
    - 100. Bombing in Lebanon/Grenada "Rescue Mission"/Jesse Jackson/Baby Jane Doe 5 Nov 1983 (Box 51)
    - 101. Reagan's Popularity/Elections/Middle East Crisis/Learning Government Secrets 12 Nov 1983 (Box 51)
    - 102. France, Israel, and Lebanon/Presidential Campaign/Deficit/Movie The Day After19 Nov 1983 (Box 51)
    - 103. Soviet Warning re Deployment in Europe/U.S.-Israeli Relations/Nicaragua/ The Day After26 Nov 1983 (Box 51)
    - 104. Reappraisal of U.S. Middle East Poreign Policy/U.S. Military Aid Bill/Price Supports for Dairy Farmers/Speakers & Feldstein 3 Dec 1983 (Box 51)
    - 105. Marines in Lebanon/Strategic Arms Talks/Civil Rights Commission/Economic Advisor/American Education 10 Dec 1983 (Box 51)
    - 106. Christmas Observations/Lebanese Crisis/U.S. Military Strength/South Carolina Rape Case 17 Dec 1983 (Box 51)
    - 107. Civilian & Military Conduct in Beirut/PLO/Economic Future/Prospects for Peace 24 Dec 1983 (Box 51)
    - 108. Prospects for 1984 31 Dec 1983 (Box 51)
    - 109. Reappraisal of U.S. Policy in Lebanon and at Home/Kissinger Commission/The Economy/USIA Director Witt 7 Jan 1984 (Box 51)
    - 110. Diplomatic Relations with the Vatican/Chinese Premier visits Reagan/Three Reports from Presidential Commissions 14 Jan 1984 (Box 51)
    - 111. Reagan Reelection/Soviet Union/Civil rights Commission/Supreme Court and TV taping 21 Jan 1984 (Box 51)
    - 112. State of the Union Address 28 Jan 1984 (Box 51)
    - 113. President's Budget/Marines in Lebanon/Shultz and Nicaragua/Democratic Presidential Campaign 4 Feb 1984 (Box 51)
    - 114. Lebanon/Soviet leadership/Democratic Presidential Campaign 11 Feb 1984 (Box 51)
    - 115. Andropov is Dead/Lebanese Crisis/Budget Deficit/USIA Black List 11 Feb 1984 (Box 51)
    - 116. Marines leaving Lebanon/Iowa Caucus/The Budget/Census Bureau 25 Feb 1984 (Box 51)
    - 117. New Hampshire Primary/Shultz and Lebanon/Edwin Meese Nomination 3 Mar 1984 (Box 51)
    - 118. Democratic Presidential Contest/School Prayer Amendment/Aid for Nicaragua and El Salvador 10 Mar 1984 (Box 51)
    - 119. Reappraisal of Democratic Presidential Race/Silent Prayer in Schools/Meese as Attorney General/Voters and Pollsters 17 Mar 1984 (Box 51)
    - 120. Meese Nomination/Democratic Presidential Race/Public School Prayer 24 Mar 1984 (Box 51)
    - 121. Hart-Mondale Competition/El Salvador/1979 SALT Agreement 31 Mar 1984 (Box 51)
    - 122. Foreign Policy Problems/Aid for El Salvador & Nicaragua/Pennsylvania Primary/Racial Issue 7 Apr 1984 (Box 51)
    - 123. Nicaragua & Congress/World Court Decision on Central America/Saudi Arabia and the CIA/Democratic Presidential Contest 14 Apr 1984 (Box 51)
    - 124. U.S. Aid to Central America/Reagan's Visit to Peking/Missouri Caucus/Chrysler Profits 21 Apr 1984 (Box 51)
    - 125. Peking Trip/Democratic Campaign/CIA Operations in Central America/Bills to Combat Terrorism 28 Apr 1984 (Box 51)
    - 126. Auto Industry and Quota Protection/Democratic Campaign/Peking Trip 5 May 1984 (Box 51)
    - 127. Communist Boycott of Olympics/Reagan Victory in House/Cary Hart/Feldstein Resignation 12 May 1984 (Box 51)
    - 128. Diplomacy or Force/Nerve Gas Weapons/Budget Deficit/Florida House of Representatives 19 May 1984 (Box 51)
    - 129. Persian Gulf Crisis/House Votes on Aid/CIA and William Casey 27 May 1984 (Box 51)
    - 130. Democratic Primary Season/President's European Trip/Soviet Dissident/Persian Gulf/Smoking Bans 2 Jun 1984 (Box 51)
    - 131. Mondale/European Trip/National Drinking Age 9 Jun 1984 (Box 51)
    - 132. Summit Meeting/Supreme Court Decisions/Mondale and running Mates 16 Jun 1984 (Box 51)
    - 133. Immigration Bill/Mondale Platform/Legal Drinking Age Debate 23 Jun 1984 (Box 51)
    - 134. Jesse Jackson/American & Cuban Prisoner Release/Mondale & Hart/Regulations on TV News and Commercials 30 Jun 1984 (Box 51)
    - 135. Supreme Court Decisions/Vice President Search/Jackson's Foreign Missions 7 Jul 1984 (Box 51)
    - 136. Gerarldine Ferraro-Mondale's Running Mate 14 Jul 1984 (Box 51)
    - 137. Democratic Convention 21 Jul 1984 (Box 51)
    - 138. Reagan Re-election/Vanessa Williams Controversy 28 Jul 1984 (Box 51)
    - 139. Concerns of August 4 Aug 1984 (Box 51)
    - 140. Taxes as Campaign Issue/Abortion Policy/Legacy of Nixon 11 Aug 1984 (Box 51)
    - 141. Gerldine Ferraro/Republican Convention/Delorian Verdict 18 Aug 1984 (Box 51)
    - 142. Republican Convention/Ferraro Financial Disclosures 25 Aug 1984 (Box 51)
    - 143. Presidential Campaign/Soviet Leadership 1 Sep 1984 (Box 51)
    - 144. Reagan vs. Mondale/Canadian Elections 8 Sep 1984, Note: Tape is damaged at the beginning (Box 51)
    - 145. Reagan's Lead over Mondale in the Polls/Governor Cuomo's Speech re Abortion and Speration of Church & State/Gromyko 15 Sep 1984 (Box 52)
    - 146. Second Bombing in Beirut Embassy/Reagan's Lead over Mondale/Supreme Court Justice Blackmun Declares Court Too Right Wing 22 Sep 1984 (Box 52)
    - 147. Reagan-Gromyko Meeting 29 Sep 1984 (Box 52)
    - 148. Reagan's Commanding Lead Heading into the Debate/Donovan Steps Aside 6 Oct 1984 (Box 52)
    - 149. Presidential & Vice-Presidential Debates 13 Oct 1984 (Box 52)
    - 150. CIA Training Pamphlet in Terrorist Activities/Chernenko re Arms Control/U.S.-Soviet Relations 20 Oct 1984 (Box 52)
    - 151. Reagan & Mondale Race/ Anniversary of the Beirut Bombing and Grenada/Force Against Terrorism 27 Oct 1984 (Box 52)
    - 152. Projections re Elections/Assassination of Indira Gandhi 3 Nov 1984 (Box 52)
    - 153. Reagan's Re-election/Lack of a General Sweep of Offices by the Republicans 10 Nov 1984 (Box 52)
    - 154. Tax Increases?/Nicaragua/Nuclear Arms Control/U.S. Bishops Pastoral Letter 17 Nov 1984 (Box 52)
    - 155. U.S.-Soviet Arms Talks 24 Nov 1984 (Box 52)
    - 156. Senate Republican Leaders/Sec. Weinberger's Rules for Military Intervention 1 Dec 1984 (Box 52)
    - 157. Budget/Taxes/South African Policies 8 Dec 1984 (Box 52)
    - 158. Reduction of the Deficit Without Reducing Defense Spending 15 Dec 1984 (Box 52)
    - 159. Weinberger vs. the Press over a Secret Space Mission 22 Dec 1984 (Box 52)
    - 160. Look Back and Ahead 29 Dec 1984 (Box 52)
    - 161. Congress Goes Back to Work/Vigilante Justice 5 Jan 1985 (Box 52)
    - 162. Nuclear Arms Control/Social Security/Jesse Helms and TV Anchormen 12 Jan 1985 (Box 52)
    - 163. Eve of Reagan's Inauguration 19 Jan 1985 (Box 52)
    - 164. Congress' Reaction to Reagan's Inaugural Address 26 Jan 1985 (Box 52)
    - 165. Congress & the New Budget/Confirmation of Edwin Meese 2 Feb 1985 (Box 52)
    - 166. Proper Role of the Federal Government and the Budget, Especially Farmers 9 Feb 1985 (Box 52)
    - 167. President's Role in the Commemoration of the 40th Anniversary of the End of WW II 16 Feb 1985 (Box 52)
    - 168. Strong Denunciation of Nicaragua/CBS-Westmoreland Court Case/Supreme Court Decision re State Vs. Federal Rights 23 Feb 1985 (Box 52)
    - 169. Nicaragua/Aid to Farmers/Aid to Education/MX Missile 2 Mar 1985 (Box 52)
    - 170. Veto of Farm Bill/Senate Budget Committee/"Bash the Media" Season in Washington 9 Mar 1985 (Box 52)
    - 171. New Man in the Kremlin 16 Mar 1985 (Box 52)
    - 172. Reagan Victory in the Senate-MX Missile/Ohio Savings and Loan Crisis/Labor Secretary/South Africa 23 Mar 1985 (Box 52)
    - 173. MX Missile/Japanese Auto Imports/Bernard Goetz 30 Mar 1985 (Box 52)
    - 174. BLANK TAPE 6 Apr 1985 (Box 52)
    - 175. U.S.-Soviet Summit/President's Visit to West German War Graves/Two Court Decisions 13 Apr 1985 (Box 52)
    - 176. House-No to Contra Aid/Budget Debate 27 Apr 1985 (Box 52)
    - 177. Bonn & Bitbury Visits/Economic Sanctions Vs. Nicaragua/The Budget/Presidential Appointments/White-collar Crime 4 May 1985 (Box 52)
    - 178. European Trip/Budget/White-collar Crime 11 May 1985 (Box 52)
    - 179. Troubles With Savings & Loans and Banks/Defense Budget Proposals/Terrorism 18 May 1985 (Box 52)
    - 180. The Navy and Phony Billing/Budget Policy Conflicts/Shultz re Nicaragua 25 May 1985 (Box 52)
    - 181. Tax Reform Proposal/Brussels Soccer Riot 1 Jun 1985 (Box 52)
    - 182. School Prayer/Aid to Contras/SALT II/Walker Family 8 Jun 1985 (Box 52)
    - 183. SALT II/Contras/Bill Proposing Death to Spies 15 Jun 1985 (Box 52)
    - 184. American Hostages in the Middle East 22 Jun 1985 (Box 52)
    - 185. Hostage Crisis/William Reynolds Nomination/David Stockman Comment on Taxes 29 Jun 1985 (Box 52)
    - 186. Hostage Crisis/U.S.-Soviet Summit/Public Funds and Parochial Schools 6 Jul 1985 (Box 52)
    - 187. Budget, Tax Reform, and Deficit/Terrorism/South African Apartheid Policy/Coca-cola 13 Jul 1985 (Box 52)